Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 10 and District 10 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 10 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1412
    - Local 1412 General Cable Negotiations, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Brant to Matles with Tentative Agreement, August 28, 1943; 2.
      - Matles to Brant, September 4, 1943; 3.
      - Brant to Matles, September 4, 1943; 4.
      - Matles to Brant, September 7, 1943; 5.
      - Brant to Matles with Tentative Agreement and Points of Disagreement, September 8, 1943; 6.
      - Brant to Omar Hoskins, September 9, 1943; 7.
    - Local 1412 GE Grievances (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Carl Brant to James Matles, August 25, 1943; 1.
      - Matles to Brant, September 8, 1943; 2.
      - Brant to Julius Emspak, January 3, 1944; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau to Brant, January 13, 1944; 4.
    - Local 1412 Heintz & Kaufman Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Chronology, December 1943; 1.
      - Carl Brant to Allan Gifford, December 30, 1943; 2.
      - Brant to Julius Emspak, January 6, 1944; 3.
      - Brant to Emspak, January 12, 1944; 4.
      - Brant to Russ Nixon, January 20, 1944; 5.
    - Local 1412 Westinghouse Incentive Plan and War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - William Davis to Sheridan Downey, January 22, 1944; 1.
      - Downey to J.B. Kraft, January 25, 1944; 2.
    - Local 1412 Washington Organization, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - John Kraft to James Matles, July 17, 1946; 1.
      - Matles to Kraft, July 25, 1946; 2.
      - Albert Smith to Matles with Bills, September 30, 1946; 3.
    - Local 1412 Northern California Congress of Industrial Organizations Factionalism, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Joe Clark to All Congress of Industrial Organizations Locals with Minutes, Resolutions, and Mailing List Form, April 8, 1948; 1.
      - Tim Flynn to CIO Affiliates, April 9, 1948; 2.
    - Local 1412 Dura Strike, 1954-55 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Clara Fiering to Julius Emspak, November 12, 1954; 1.
      - Fiering to Emspak, November 30, 1954; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Fiering, December 2, 1954; 3.
      - Fiering to Emspak, March 3, 1955; 4.
      - Emspak to William Elconin, March 15, 1955; 5.
    - Local 1412 Correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - Gardner Employee Security Plan, April 10, 1940; 1.
      - Leo Turner to James Matles Regarding Westinghouse Contract, April 29, 1941; 2.
      - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change and Officers, March 26, 1943; 3.
      - Brant to Matles Regarding Speedup and GE Oakland Organization, April 20, 1943; 4.
      - Brant to David Scribner Regarding Emeryville Westinghouse and Bargaining Unit, October 28, 1943; 5.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Policy Contracts, July 24, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Heintz & Kaufman Strike, January 7, 1946; 7.
      - William Elconin to John Bittman Regarding Staff Members, May 25, 1946; 8.
      - Elconin to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 22, 1946; 9.
      - Sandra Martin to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Lea Case with Charges; December 4, 1947, Walt Hutzler Letter to Walter Lea; February 2, 1948, William Stevenson Letter to Lea; May 11, 1948, Memo; and April 20, 1948, George Walker Letter, May 14, 1948; 10.
    - Local 1412 Correspondence, 1950-55, undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Emma Letter to Rachie Regarding Local 1002, April 10, 1950; 1.
      - William Rubens Report Regarding Gardner Electric Contract and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, August 28, 1950; 2.
      - Ben Riskin to Carl Brant Regarding Speed-up and General Cable Rome Strike, October 10, 1950; 3.
      - Joe Dermody Memo to Janet Regarding Oakland Transformer Strike, January 29, 1951; 4.
      - James Matles to William Elconin Regarding GE Oakland Inter-union Rivalry, October 14, 1952; 5.
      - Sandra Memo to General Cable Strikers Regarding Strike, October 6, 1952; 6.
      - Elconin to Dermody Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, June 16, 1955; 7.
      - Richard Ettinger Letter Regarding Organization of White Collar Workers, n.d.; 8.
    - Local 1412 Correspondence, 1967-1979 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Local 1412 Correspondence, 1956-1974 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Local 1412 Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Local 1412 Oakland Westinghouse Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Local 1412 Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Local 1412 Misappropriated Money, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Local 1412 Oakland, CA, 1956-1967 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Local 1413
    - Local 1413 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937-May 1938 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Local 1413 Reports of Financial Secretary, June 1937-March 1938 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Local 1413 Per Capita Reports, November 1937-April 1938 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Local 1413 Publications, 1938, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Berger Bakke to Members Pamphlet Regarding Organization, January 15, 1938; 1.
      - "Membership Meeting" Leaflet, n.d.; 2.
    - Local 1413 George Beisey Closing (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - V.R. Kennedy to Gerard Swope, May 19, 1938; 1.
      - Local 1413 to Dealers, May 20, 1938; 2.
      - Kennedy to James Carey, May 21, 1938; 3.
    - Local 1413 Leaflets, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - MacBeth to Local 1414 Regarding Organization, January 6, 1938; 1.
      - Election Extra Regarding Organization, January 1938; 2.
      - "CIO Marches On" Regarding Organization, February 1938; 3.
      - "Drive Em In" Regarding Organization, March 1938; 4.
    - Local 1413 Pamphlet, Victory Bulletin, January 1938 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Local 1418
    - Local 1418 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - J.R. Bell to Earl Keeler Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, September 30, 1939; 1.
      - James Carey to Leo Stockwell Regarding Projectionists Organization, August 19, 1937; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to A.W. Lindstrom Regarding Unemployment, December 30, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to C.G. Carlson Regarding Per Capita, April 22, 1940; 4.
      - Emspak to Carlson Regarding Per Capita, May 24, 1940; 5.
      - James Matles to Stockwell Regarding Finances, May 12, 1941; 6.
    - Local 1418 Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - W.L. Baynes to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, April 8, 1938; 1.
      - C.G. Carlson to UE Regarding Finances, March 13, 1940; 2.
      - Carlson to UE Regarding Per Capita, May 10, 1940; 3.
      - E.W. Keeler to Emspak Regarding Officers, June 2, 1938; 4.
      - Helio Kennedy to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, October 23, 1939; 5.
      - Adolph Lindstrom to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, January 1939; 6.
      - Leo Stockwell to James Carey Regarding Organization and International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees Inter-union Rivalry, August 14, 1937; 7.
      - Stockwell to Carey Regarding Organization and IATSE Inter-union Rivalry, August 1937; 8.
      - Stockwell to James Matles Regarding Finances and IATSE Inter-union Rivalry, April 24, 1941; 9.
      - Stockwell to Matles Regarding Finances and IATSE Inter-union Rivalry, May 17, 1941; 10.
    - Local 1418 Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, November 1937-August 1939 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Local 1418 Reports of Financial Secretary, May-November 1937 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Local 1418 Per Capita Reports, October 1937-July 1940 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Local 1418 Chester Expulsion (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Ed Chester to John L. Lewis, February 3, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Ed Chester, February 20, 1940; 2.
      - Chester to Empsak, March 1940; 3.
      - Leo Turner to Emspak, February 28, 1940; 4.
      - Chester to Emspak, May 31, 1940; 5.
      - Chester to James Carey, September 4, 1940; 6.
  - Local 1421
    - Local 1421 Constitutions, May 17, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Local 1421 Officers Lists, January 1940-February 1941 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Local 1421 Officers Minutes, November 22, 1938-November 21, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Local 1421 Officers Resolutions, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Officer Resolution Regarding Organization and Staff Members, 1.
      - Officer Resolution Regarding Wages and Hours, 2.
    - Local 1421 Membership Minutes, January 17-November 7, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Local 1421 Membership Resolutions, 1941-1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Membership Resolution Regarding GE Service Wages, January 17, 1941; 1.
      - Membership Resolution Regarding GE Service and International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees Inter-union Rivalry, August 5, 1941; 2.
      - Membership Resolution Regarding China, September 17, 1946; 3.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - J.R. Albin to Local 1421 Regarding U.S. Flourescent Lighting and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 16, 1941; 1.
      - Janet Barish to Lucia Geiselman, February 7, 1947; 2.
      - Edwin Beal to Local 1421 Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, May 19, 1942; 3.
      - Beal to Local 1421 Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, June 25, 1942; 4.
      - James Carey to Michael Weiss Regarding GE Service Organization, December 12, 1939; 5.
      - Joe Dermody to Weiss Regarding GE Seniority, May 5, 1944; 6.
      - Lyle Dowling to Lynn Gunther Regarding Subcontracting, November 14, 1941; 7.
      - Julius Emspak to W.G. Hornbostel Regarding Dues, November 6, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak to Hornbostel Regarding Per Capita, April 21, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak to Hornbostel Regarding Per Capita, January 13, 1939; 10.
      - Emspak to Hornbostel Regarding Dues, March 2, 1939; 11.
      - Emspak to Hornbostel Regarding Dues, May 19, 1939; 12.
      - Emspak to Local 1421 Regarding Dues, June 26, 1939; 13.
      - Emspak to R.E. Reeder Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, September 14, 1939; 14.
      - Emspak to F. Temple Regarding Per Capita, September 21, 1939; 15.
      - Emspak to M. Weiss Regarding GE Grievance, February 2, 1940; 16.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding Pensions, Wages, and GE, March 20, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding Wages, April 25, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak to Celia Lewis Regarding Electrolux Boycott, February 20, 1941; 19.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding Wages, March 11, 1941; 20.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding Draftsmen Organization, March 22, 1941; 21.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Julius Emspak to Michael Weiss Regarding GE Wages, April 18, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Carl Brant Regarding Columbia Strike, May 7, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Jim Burford Regarding Columbia Strike, May 8, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Lynn Gunther Regarding Local 1421 Constitution, October 27, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Joe Marty Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 25, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding GE Overtime and War Labor Board, October 30, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Celia Lewis Regarding Per Capita, July 13, 1943; 7.
      - Emspak to Lewis Regarding Finances, December 13, 1943; 8.
      - Emspak to Lewis Regarding Finances, February 24, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Carl Brant Regarding Finances, May 4, 1944; 10.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Finances, May 11, 1944; 11.
      - Emspak to Lewis Regarding Dues and Veterans, May 31, 1944; 12.
      - Emspak to Lewis Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 6, 1945; 13.
      - Emspak to Frank Spector Regarding Adventists, March 6, 1945; 14.
      - Emspak to Roberta Jones Regarding Membership Drive, April 22, 1946; 15.
      - Emspak to Jones Regarding U.S. Motors Strike, May 11, 1946; 16.
      - Emspak to Jones Regarding Finances, May 21, 1946; 17.
      - Emspak to Lucia Geiselman Regarding Finances, September 25, 1946; 18.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Capitol Records Strike, August 26, 1947; 19.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Strike Fund, April 20, 1948; 20.
      - Emspak to Weiss Regarding Mullenback Electric and Sterling Electric Strike, July 13, 1948; 21.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Sterling Electric Strike, August 23, 1948; 22.
      - Emspak to Mildrid Halverson Regarding United Steelworkers, December 21, 1949; 23.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Per Capita, August 28, 1950; 24.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Per Capita, October 26, 1950; 25.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Julius Emspak to Jacob Soloman Regarding Publicity, April 11, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Carl Brant Regarding Pryne Strike, September 11, 1951; 2.
      - Emspak to Andrea Carrasco Regarding Per Capita and Pryne Strike, October 10, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Pryne Strike, October 31, 1951; 4.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding General Cable Strike, September 22, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Johnson Expulsion and Factionalism, April 6, 1953; 6.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Per Capita, April 9, 1953; 7.
      - Emspak to C. Hartford Regarding Per Capita, October 21, 1953; 8.
      - Emspak to Delmar Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, March 4, 1954; 9.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, March 11, 1954; 10.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, March 19, 1954; 11.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, March 26, 1954; 12.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, April 5, 1954; 13.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, April 16, 1954; 14.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Dura Steel Strike, April 22, 1954; 15.
      - Emspak to Tucker Regarding Quinn-Emspak Case, May 31, 1955; 16.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1952 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Delmar Tucker Regarding Square D Negotiation, March 22, 1950; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Carl Brant Regarding General Cable Strike, November 25, 1952; 2.
      - George Foulk to Helio Kennedy Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, October 20, 1938; 3.
      - Sidney Gilbert to Martha Hard Regarding Wages and War Labor Board, February 11, 1944; 4.
      - Gilbert to Hard Regarding WLB and Decca, May 23, 1944; 5.
      - Robert Liusky to Hard Regarding US Motors Strike and US Motors Milford Organization, November 12, 1945; 6.
      - Frederick Livingston to Hard Regarding Construction and Maintenance of Membership, October 16, 1944; 7.
      - Livingston to Hard Regarding Maintenance of Membership with Arbitration Case, October 23, 1944; 8.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - James Matles to W.J. Hornbostel Regarding Phelps Dodge Organization, September 20, 1937; 1.
      - Matles to Hornbostel Regarding Phelps Dodge Contract with November 9, 1937, Wylie Brown Letter to William Mitchell, November 11, 1937; 2.
      - Matles to Hornbostel Regarding Phelps Dodge Organization, November 15, 1937; 3.
      - Matles to Hornbostel Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, April 12, 1938; 4.
      - Matles to Hornbostel Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation and Factionalism, April 22, 1938; 5.
      - Matles to R.E. Reeder Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and Phelps Dodge Negotiation, June 24, 1938; 6.
      - Matles to Reeder Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, August 30, 1938; 7.
      - Matles to Helio Kennedy Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, October 24, 1938; 8.
      - Matles to Kennedy Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, November 3, 1938; 9.
      - Matles to F. Temple Regarding Organization, August 24, 1939; 10.
      - Matles to Reeder Regarding Government Contract, August 31, 1939; 11.
      - Matles to Reeder Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, September 27, 1939; 12.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1954 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - James Matles to Robert Reeder Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, November 8, 1939; 1.
      - Matles to Millard Nichols Regarding Staff Members, April 10, 1940; 2.
      - Matles to Michael Weiss Regarding GE Negotiation, April 13, 1940; 3.
      - Matles to Reeder Regarding Phelps Dodge Organization, December 9, 1940; 4.
      - Matles to Frank Lopez Regarding UE News, December 17, 1940; 5.
      - Matles to Lynn Gunther Regarding Phelps Dodge Negotiation, August 12, 1941; 6.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding Sheet Metal Products Contract, September 2, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding Thrifty Sheet Metal and California Sheet Metal Contract, September 10, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, September 18, 1941; 9.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding Phelps Dodge Wages, September 18, 1941; 10.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding Metropolitan Sheet Metal Negotiation, October 6, 1941; 11.
      - Matles to Gunther Regarding Phelps Dodge Wages, October 7, 1941; 12.
      - Matles to Weiss Regarding US Motors Strike, May 13, 1946; 13.
      - Matles to Local 1412 Regarding Staff Members, July 8, 1946; 14.
      - Matles to Lloyd Van Dyke Regarding Twentieth Century Record Organization, August 21, 1946; 15.
      - Matles to Delmar Tucker Regarding Dura Strike, February 16, 1954; 16.
    - Local 1421 Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Russ Nixon to Carl Brant Regarding PAC, September 8, 1947; 1.
      - Nixon to Brant Regarding Political Action, October 30, 1947; 2.
      - Ben Riskin to Roberta Jones Regarding Political Action, April 14, 1946; 3.
      - Riskin to Martha Hard Regarding Veterans and General Cable, June 25, 1946; 4.
      - Riskin to Hard Regarding Veterans General Cable, June 25, 1946; 5.
      - Riskin to Hard Regarding General Cable White Collar Organization, June 27, 1946; 6.
      - Riskin to Brant Regarding General Cable White Collar Negotiation, August 28, 1946; 7.
      - Riskin to Carl Brant Regarding RCA and Staff Members, April 4, 1952; 8.
      - David Scribner to Frank Spector Regarding National Labor Relations Board, September 11, 1945; 9.
      - Scribner to Lucia Geiselman Regarding Political Action, September 25, 1946; 10.
      - Scribner to Brant Regarding RCA, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and NLRB, July 2, 1952; 11.
      - William Sentner to Martha Hard Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, June 2, 1944; 12.
      - Sentner to Hard Regarding Staff Members, August 8, 1945; 13.
      - H.A. Simpson to Michael Weiss Regarding GE Grievances, October 9, 1942; 14.
      - A.N. Towsen to Lloyd Van Dycke Regarding Columbia Records and Decca Records Contract, February 3, 1944; 15.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Leo Baefsky to UE Regarding Dues, December 1, 1948; 1.
      - Thomas Beam to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, August 24, 1943; 2.
      - Carl Brant to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 1102, March 12, 1947; 3.
      - Brant to Harry Truman Regarding Foreign Policy, March 14, 1947; 4.
      - Brant to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Domestic Thermostat Strike, April 14, 1947; 5.
      - Brant to Schwellenbach Regarding Domestic Thermostat Strike, April 17, 1947; 6.
      - Brant to Schwellenbach Regarding Square D Negotiation, April 17, 1947; 7-8.
      - Brant to Schwellenbach Regarding Allied Record Negotiation, April 18, 1947; 9.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Political Action, May 16, 1947; 10.
      - Brant to Nat Spero Regarding Taft Hartley, June 25, 1947; 11.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Capitol Records Lockout, August 15, 1947; 12.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Capitol Records, August 18, 1947; 13.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Capitol Records Lockout, August 22, 1947; 14.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Capitol Records Lockout, August 29, 1947; 15.
      - Brant to UE Regarding Political Action, October 6, 1947; 16.
      - Brant to UE Regarding Political Action, October 15, 1947; 17.
      - Brant to Sidney Gilbert Regarding Decca Contract, December 2, 1947; 18.
      - Brant to Charles Kelly Regarding Square D Negotiation, December 12, 1947; 19.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Record Companies Negotiation, December 10, 1947; 20.
      - Brant to UE Regarding Political Action, December 17, 1947; 21.
      - Brant to Kelly Regarding Square D Negotiation, January 15, 1948; 22.
      - Brant to Philip Murray Regarding Political Action, January 16, 1948; 23.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry Negotiation, April 15, 1948; 24.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak Regarding Mullenbach & Sterling Electric Strike, July 19, 1948; 1.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Mullenbach & Sterling Strike and United Steelworkers Inter-union Rivalry, August 11, 1948; 2.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Mullenbach & Sterling Electric Strike, August 27, 1948; 3.
      - Brant to Harry Truman Regarding Red-baiting, October 4, 1948; 4.
      - Brant to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Morris Metal Products Organization and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, February 7, 1949; 5.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Inter-union Rivalry, June 30, 1949; 6.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding USWA and United Mine Workers of America Strikes, October 27, 1949; 7.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Red-baiting and McCarran Act, October 30, 1949; 8.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Smith Meter Transfer and Local 1004, December 27, 1950; 9.
      - Brant to James Matles Regarding Labor Unity, January 10, 1951; 10.
      - Brant to H. De Voe Rea Regarding Pryne Negotiation, July 6, 1951; 11.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Pryne Strike, July 16, 1951; 12.
      - Brant to Matles Regarding Pryne Strike, August 24, 1951; 13.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Pryne Strike, September 28, 1951; 14.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Pryne Strike, October 23, 1951; 15.
      - Brant to Lloyd Willard Regarding Columbia Negotiation and Local 237, May 26, 1952; 16.
      - Brant to David Scribner Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and RCA Inter-union Rivalry, June 30, 1952; 17.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding General Cable Strike, September 3, 1952; 18.
      - Brant to UE Regarding Westinghouse Nutall Strike, September 5, 1952; 19.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, October 22, 1952; 20.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding General Cable Strike, November 6, 1952; 21.
    - Local 1421 Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Carl Brant to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 31, 1953; 1.
      - Brant to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 10, 1953; 2.
      - Brant to Joseph Turkowski Regarding Decca Negotiation, May 11, 1953; 3.
      - Brant to Ben Riskin Regarding General Cable Negotiation, December 10, 1953; 4.
      - James Burford to James Matles Regarding Columbia Recording Strike, April 27, 1941; 5.
      - Burford to Emspak Regarding Columbia Recording Strike, April 28, 1941; 6.
      - Burford to James Matles Regarding Columbia Recording Strike, April 30, 1941; 7.
      - Burford to Matles Regarding Columbia Recording Strike and RCA Hollywood Organization, May 2, 1941; 8.
      - Burford to Matles Regarding Columbia Recording Strike, May 5, 1941; 9.
      - Burford to Emspak Regarding Columbia Strike, May 19, 1941; 10.
      - Alex Chacon to Emspak Regarding Dura Steel Strike, February 1, 1954; 11.
      - Chacon to All UE Locals Regarding Dura Steel Strike, April 16, 1954; 12.
      - Lucia Geiselman to Emspak Regarding Political Action, September 18, 1946; 13.
      - Geiselman to Emspak Regarding Political Action, September 20, 1946; 14.
      - Geiselman to David Scribner Regarding Constitutions and Political Action, September 20, 1946; 15.